### SHIN HWEI TAN

Contact Information School of Computing Block COM1, #01-16 13 Computing Drive

Mobile: +65-91203168

Email: shinhwei@comp.nus.edu.sg

Singapore 117417 Website: http://www.comp.nus.edu.sg/~shinhwei/

Research Interests My current research is mainly focused on program testing and program repair. I have proposed new methods and developed research tools to facilitate dynamic code comment analysis using test case generation tool. I am currently looking at improving the existing techniques for program repair.

Education

### National University of Singapore, Singapore

Ph.D., School of Computing, August 2012-present

- Thesis Topic: Automated repair of software regressions
- Adviser: Abhik Roychoudhury
- Current CAP: 4.5/5.00

### University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, Champaign, IL

M.S., Computer Science, May 2012

- Thesis Topic: @tComment: Testing Javadoc Comments to Detect Comment-Code Inconsistencies
- Advisers:
  - Darko Marinov
  - Lin Tan
- Overall GPA: 3.91/4.00

B.S.(Hons), Computer Science, May 2010

- Thesis Topic: Theories/Parameterized tests for JUnit
- Adviser: Darko Marinov
- Overall GPA: 3.68/4.00

#### Conference Publications

- 1. J. Yi, D. Qi, S. H. Tan, A. Roychoudhury. Expressing and Checking Intended Changes via Software Change Contracts. In: International Symposium on Software Testing and Analysis (ISSTA 2013), pages TO APPEAR, Lugano, Switzerland, July 2013. (acceptance: 26%, 32/124)
- S. H. Tan, D. Marinov, L. Tan, and G. T. Leavens. @tComment: Testing Javadoc Comments to Detect Comment-Code Inconsistencies. In: International Conference on Software Testing, Verification, and Validation (ICST 2012), pages 260-269, Montreal, Canada, April 2012. (acceptance: 27%, 39/145)
- 3. B. Daniel, D. Dig, T. Gvero, V. Jagannath, J. Jiaa, D. Mitchell, J. Nogiec, S. H. Tan, and D. Marinov. ReAssert: A Tool for Repairing Broken Unit Tests. In: International Conference on Software Engineering, Demonstrations Track (ICSE Demo 2011), pages 1010-1012, Honolulu, HI, May 2011. (acceptance: 37%, 22/60)

Professional Activities Conference Presentations

- ISSTA 2014, Artifact Evaluation Committee
- ICST 2012, regular paper track, Montreal, Canada. (April 17-21, 2012)

# Teaching Experience

### University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, Champaign, IL

*Teaching Assistant*, August 2010 to May 2012

Teaching Assistant for CS242: Programming Studio Laboratory

- Spring 2012 (2 sections)
- Responsible for supervision of programming assignments presentation for 5-6 students per section

Teaching Assistant for CS427: Software Engineering I

- Fall 2010 and Fall 2011
- Responsible for 1-hour supervision of 2-hour office hours.
- Graded bi-weekly programming assignments for 20 groups of students

Teaching Assistant for CS428: Software Engineering II

- Spring 2011
- Provided support for online students through the Illinois Internet Computer Science Program(I2CS)
- Graded bi-weekly programming assignments for 20 groups of students

Undergraduate Assistant for Railroad Department, August 2007 to May 2009

- Carried out an independent project on automated web retrieval
- Maintained MS Access database for daily tank car accident reports
- Debugged and programmed using Visual Basic, Ruby and HTML

# Working Experience

### Intel Corporation, Penang, Malaysia

Summer Intern for Testing Hole Resolution(THR) June 2011 to August 2011

- Developed and implemented automation for MS Windows script automation engine to improve efficiency in running automated tests.
- Implemented features and developed error handling for program featuring Perl, AutoIt and Tcl

# Awards and Honors

- David J. Kuck Outstanding MS Thesis Award (2013)
- Singapore International Graduate Award (2012-2015)
- ACM-W Scholarship (2012)
- Malaysian Government Scholarship (2006-2010)
- Rockwell Collins Scholarship (2009)
- Motorola Academic Scholarship (2008)

#### Software Skills

Computer Programming:

• Java, C, C++, Visual Basic, Matlab

Version Control and Software Configuration Management:

• DVCS (Mercurial/MO, Git/StGit), and VCS (CVS, SVN)

Software Test:

• Randoop, JUnit

#### Language Skills

Fluent in Mandarin, Cantonese, English and Malay